all right the curtains are drawing back
窗帘正在退缩
here in our theater in this hour we will
我们将在这个时间在我们的剧院
view film of an actual counseling
观看实际咨询的电影
session
会议
with John Street counseling a young
与约翰街一起为年轻人提供咨询
couple in this first segment we will see
我们将看到第一部分的情侣
the first 16 minutes of the very first
的第16分钟的第一个
session well Joe and Julie I'm very
乔和朱莉我很好
happy about the fact that you've come in
对你进来的事实感到高兴
to see me today and I hope that we can
今天见到我，我希望我们能
address some of the issues that you're
解决你遇到的 一些问题
facing in your life and in your ministry
面对你的生活和你的事工
individually and I want to take you to
个别而且我想带你去
the Word of God and help you to see how
上帝的话语，帮助你看看如何
God has answers for these problems let's
上帝有这些问题的 答案
begin with prayer let's seek his help in
从祷告开始让我们寻求他的帮助
this counseling process shall we
我们这个咨询过程
gracious father we we come before you as
亲切的父亲，我们来到你面前
creatures who realize our own phal
实现我们自己的phal的生物
ability we understand that we are people
我们能够理解我们是人
who also are sinful and because of that
谁也罪孽深重的，因为这
we have a tendency to stray from you and
我们倾向于偏离你和你
stray from your word and so that's the
从你的话偏离，因此这就是
reason why at the beginning of this
之所以在今年年初
particular time together with Joe and
特别是乔和乔一起
Julie we ask for your help in this
朱莉，我们要求在 此 您的帮助
process we we know that you're a God who
过程我们知道你是一个上帝
gives hope when you know that you are
当你知道自己的时候会给予希望
God who gives comfort that's the way in
给予安慰的上帝
fact the Apostle Paul describes you in
事实上，使徒保罗描述了在
Romans 15 that you were the God of all
罗马书15 ，你是所有人的上帝
comfort and we know that both Joe and
舒适，我们知道乔和
Julie have gone through some difficult
朱莉经历了一些困难
times in these more recent days and
在这些最近的日子里和
they're confused and I pray father that
他们很困惑，我祈祷父亲
you will help us address the core issues
您将帮助我们解决核心问题
of these problems and give them a sense
这些问题并给他们一个感觉
that God doesn't have one of the answers
上帝没有其中一个答案
he's got the only answer for these
他得到了这些唯一的答案
problems so help us as we seek to deal
在我们寻求交易时帮助我们的问题
with this today in Christ's name Amen
今天在基督的名字阿门
well Joe and Julie you sent in and I
好的乔和朱莉你和我一起送了
really appreciate you doing this your
非常感谢你这样做你的
personal data inventories and so I've
个人数据库存，所以我
had a chance a little bit to study
有机会学习一点
what's going on in your life and I think
我认为你生活中发生了什么
Joe I'm actually going to begin with you
乔，我实际上将从你开始
and talk with you just a little bit
和你说话，只是一 点点
about what you've put down your personal
关于你放下个人的东西
data inventory and then Julie I want to
数据库存然后朱莉我想
talk with you as well you recently
最近和你谈谈你
graduated from seminary last few years
最近几年从神学院毕业
and now you're into your first pastor it
现在你成了你的第一位牧师吧
is that right that's right
是的，这是正确的
so is it pretty busy it's been full of
所以它很忙，它已经充满了
ministry and great opportunities to
事工和很好的机会
serve the body of the Lord mm-hmm
服务于主的身体mm-hmm
that's great I'm sure it's full of
这很棒，我确信它充满了
challenges as well right well we've gone
正确的挑战我们已经走了
over the honeymoon stage and we're just
在蜜月阶段，我们只是
starting to enter some of those
开始进入其中一些
challenges now as new responsibilities
现在挑战新的责任
come up and opportunities to minister to
拿出和机会去服侍
hurting people and I minister to the
伤害人民，我服务于
needs of the Saints there yeah one you
圣徒的需要在那里你是一个人
know I admire guys like you like I
知道我钦佩男人喜欢你喜欢我
remember that being in your shoes how
记得你的鞋子怎么样
many years ago and the excitement of
许多年前和兴奋的
entering and the that ministry and all
进入和那部和所有
the new responsibilities I had to take
我不得不承担新的责任
on so I I understand the pressures of
就这么II理解的压力
that now I understand you guys are
现在我明白你们了
expecting your first child is that right
期待你的第一个孩子就是这样
oh that's great well congratulations to
哦，那是非常好的祝贺
both of you and how far along are you
你和你们有多远
Julie about three months about three
朱莉大约三个月大约三个月
months that's it go oh three months to
几个月就是三个月了
go okay all right so you're almost into
好吧，好吧你几乎进入了
your third trimester yeah yeah well good
你的第三个三个月是的，好的
well this is also an exciting time too
嗯，这也是一个令人兴奋的时间太长
and also we'll introduce a whole new
而且我们将介绍一个全新的
series of pressures into your life as
一系列压力进入你的生活
well there hopefully you'll view them as
那么希望你会把它们视为
a good kind of pressure
一种很好的压力
but a lot of little challenges God has
但是上帝有很多小小的挑战
blessed me with four children and
祝福我有四个孩子和
they're getting to the age now where
他们已经到了现在的年龄
they're kind of leaving the nest and
他们那种离开巢
they're wonderful on you know den mom's
他们精彩的，你知道书房妈妈的
heart wants to hold on to them but at
心想要抓住他们，但在
the same time they've got to go out and
同时他们必须出去
start their own lives now too so well
现在开始自己的生活太好了
okay Joe one of the main reasons the two
好的乔两个主要原因之一
of you are here is because Julie's
你在这里是因为朱莉的
struggling with depression I understand
我明白与抑郁症斗争
that I know that that's probably not the
我知道这可能不是
only reason and we'll probably find that
唯一的原因，我们可能会发现
there are other issues that need to be
还有其他问题需要解决
addressed here as well so I want to be I
这里也提到了，所以我想成为我
want to be able to address everything
希望能够解决所有问题
that we can can in order to be of help
我们可以为了得到帮助
to you your health is excellent you
对你来说，你的健康状况非常好
talked a little bit about that
谈了一点
the your the church that you're
你是教会的
attending is faith community church and
参加的是信仰社区教会和
obviously your members there as well now
显然你的成员现在也在那里
getting down to a little some of the
深入了解一些
problems that you talked about in terms
你谈到的问题
of your own life Joe you talked a little
你自己的生活乔，你谈了一点
bit about anxiety that you're
关于你的焦虑
experiencing can you tell me a little
体验你能告诉我一点吗？
bit about that what do you mean by
你是说什么意思
anxiety I think just the pressures of
焦虑我认为只是压力
ministry as well as my relationship with
事工以及我与他的关系
Julie at home and even in the church I
朱莉在家里， 甚至在教堂我
have expectations of her and she seems
对她有所期待和她似乎
to always fatal and meeting those
总是致命和满足那些
expectations as far as being the
期望尽可能作为
pastor's wife that I think she should be
牧师的妻子，我认为她应该是
in the local church for we're serving we
我们在当地教堂为我们服务
have wonderful opportunities for ladies
女士们有很好的机会
ministries and whether it be calling on
各部委以及是否要求
the thought or sending little notes of
思想或发送小笔记
encouragement or sharing with the ladies
鼓励或与女士分享
and Bible studies or things she just
和圣经研究或她只是的事情
she's not rising up to meet those
她没有站起来迎接那些
expectations at all or even
所有甚至是期望
responsibilities some of the other
其中一些责任
ladies think she should be involved in
女士们认为她应该参与其中
and I see those as important way she can
我认为这些是她能够做到的重要方式
serve
服务
and not to just encourage her there but
不只是鼓励她那里，但
there hasn't been much desire at all in
还没有在所有的欲望很多
her part for that and I think just the
她的那部分，我认为只是
pressures of the challenges in our
我们面临挑战的压力
relationship maybe part of that's
关系可能是其中的一部分
related to her pregnancy and some of the
与她怀孕和一些相关
mood swings that she goes through with
情绪波动，她经过与
that or just a new pasture where she's
那个或者只是她牧场的新牧场
still trying to learn the ropes of what
仍在努力学习什么的绳索
it means to be a pastor's wife and those
它意味着成为牧师的妻子和那些人
kind of responsibilities it contributes
样的责任呢贡献
to a lot of maybe the anxiety and the
对很多人来说可能是焦虑和焦虑
desire for me to to be a wonderful
渴望我成为一个美好的人
testimony of Jesus Christ before my
前耶稣的见证我的
people and the flock where we're serving
人和我们服务的羊群
but it's a challenge and you know his
但这是一个挑战，你知道他的
first Timothy 3 says you know one of the
第一个提摩太3说你知道其中一个
biblical qualifications that I am
我是圣经的资格
accountable for to the Lord and to the
对主和对主的责任
people of God is to be sure I manage my
神的人是要确保管理我的
household well and this is a serious
家庭很好，这是一个严重的问题
concern to me in the progression of
关注我的进步
events that have taken place here to
这都发生在这里事件
reveal some of the depression in her all
揭示一些抑郁症的她所有的
right are there any other areas that you
你还有其他任何领域吗？
believe is kind of a source of your
相信是你的一种来源
anxiety or maybe we could say worry I
焦虑或者我们可以说我担心
think part of it is I've had a kind of a
想到这部分我有一个类型的
perfectionist attitude as far as maybe
完美主义的态度就可能
unrealistic expectations at time maybe
也许是不切实际的期望
some unwillingness to be as patient as I
有些人不愿意和我一样耐心
could be in letting the Lord work on
可能是让主继续工作
Julie's heart and his own timing and
朱莉的心和他自己的时间和
maybe throwing her into situations where
也许把她扔进去的地方
it may be better to be patient and allow
耐心和允许可能更好
time for her to work into that kind of
是时候让她去做那种了
mold and let her develop into the woman
模具，让她发展成女人
that got hazard to be in the church
在教堂里有危险
maybe some of my background growing up
也许我的一些背景成长
in a pastor's home I saw things one
在一个牧师的家里，我看到了一件事
particular way as a pastor's wife should
作为牧师的妻子应该特别的方式
handle things and she doesn't live up to
处理事情，她不会辜负
that right now and I want to get her
现在，我想要她
there as fast as I can and she's slow
尽可能快，她很慢
and and hasn't had that same background
而并没有相同的背景
and so part of it is just impatience I
所以它的一部分只是我的不耐烦
think and
思考和
any maturity on my own part of being
在我自己的存在上任何成熟
able to just slow down and work with her
能够放慢速度并与她合作
where she's at and be able to be
她在哪里，能够成为
thankful for the woman that God has
感谢上帝所拥有的女人
given me as she is right now
给我，因为她现在
and so I think just as unrealistic
所以我认为这是不切实际的
expectations for contributes well you
期望为您做出贡献
know I I think it's good that you see
知道我认为你看到的很好
some of those weaknesses in yourself in
你自己的一些弱点
terms of when you talk about impatience
你何时谈论不耐烦的条款
and immaturity I think it's good that
和不成熟我觉得这很好
you see that because I think that that
你看到了，因为我认为那样
we'll find out as time goes on here that
我们会发现时间在这里
some of those weaknesses that are common
其中一些 常见的弱点
weaknesses of the flesh in this type of
这种类型的肉体的弱点
situation and and at actually you're
情况，实际上你是
going to be a key asset in being
将成为存在的关键资产
assistant in assisting Julie in dealing
助理朱莉帮助交易
with this depression you're going to be
有了这种抑郁症你就会成为
key and so we want to come back to that
关键，所以我们想 回来到
and maybe talk about that a little bit
并且可能会谈一点点
later on
稍后的
now you also mark down here
现在你也在这里标记
communication what do you mean by
沟通你是什​​么意思
communication what's going on there well
沟通那里发生了什么
I think again just with the
我再想想刚刚与
responsibilities that I have I being the
我有我是责任
perfectionist and just a desire to honor
完美主义者，只是一种荣誉的愿望
the Lord and living a disciplined life I
主，并且过着有纪律的生活我
pretty much schedule my day down to
几乎安排好我的一天
every half an hour and it is penciled in
每隔半个小时就会被写下来
and I try to set aside specific time
我尝试留 出特定的时间
periods where Julie knows that I'll be
朱莉知道我会成为的时期
able to spend time with her and and yet
能够和她 共度时光
the life of the pastor I know you
牧师的生活，我认识你
understand this also that there's times
也明白这有时候了
where where there's phone calls in the
哪里哪里有在电话
middle of the day or different things
中午或不同的事情
come up and there's a counseling need
上来，这是一个咨询需求
here or a visitation somebody in the
在这里或访问某人
hospital here a number of things and
医院里有很多东西和
sometimes that can get cramped and I
有时可能会变得局促和我
know Julie gets frustrated over that and
知道朱莉对此感到沮丧
I I try to help her to understand that
我试着帮助她理解这一点
you know these things don't happen all
你知道这些事情都不会发生
the time that my desire is to spend time
我的愿望是要花费时间的时间
with her and to make time for that
和她在一起并为此腾出时间
but what that's developed into is just a
但是发展成的只是一个
communication block where we're kind of
沟通块我们有点
living two different lives in one sense
在某种意义上过着两种不同的生活
her life is not participating in the
她的生活没有参加
life of the ministry in the church where
教会在教会里的生活
I am at the same time I'm not as
我同时也不是
available as I should be to be
像我应该的那样可用
participating in her life in the home
参加她在家中的生活
and and that is cause just a barrier to
并且，这是原因只是一个障碍
be built up where she doesn't feel like
建立在她不喜欢的地方
I care or understand about where she is
我关心或了解她的位置
in the home and at the same time I feel
在家里和我同时感受到
like she has no idea of what I'm
就像她不知道我是什么
experiencing in the church and and so we
在教堂里体验，等我们
can we communicate in different terms
我们能以不同的方式沟通吗？
and there's times where I just come home
而且有时我才回家
and don't even want to say anything to
并且甚至不想说什么
her because she won't understand and
她， 因为她不会理解和
she's thinking so much about the
她想了这么多有关
homefront and her needs and and I think
我认为，居家和她的需求
there's just a lot of selfishness there
有只是很多 自私的有
it may be even some blinded nasaan my
它可能甚至是一些盲目的nasaan我的
part of failing to understand the
无法理解的部分
different trials or the different
不同的试验或不同的
circumstances that are troubling her but
困扰她的情况但是
this is what I've been called to do and
这就是我所要做的事情
I'm trying to work with her so that we
我想和她一起工作 ，使我们
can get on the same page here but our
我们可以在这里找到同一页面
communication is just kind of all over
通信只是一种遍布
the place and most of the time I I'm an
这个地方，大部分时间我都是
introvert you know when things come up
当事情发生时，你会知道内向
like this and and I noticed some
像这样，我注意到了一些
difficulties in our communication I just
我只是在沟通中遇到困难
shut down I don't want to say anything I
关闭我不想说什么我
be good I just really want to deal with
在良好的我真的想对付
things with the Lord and and she you
与主和她的事情
know really wants to try to to talk
知道真的想尝试说话
about things and and it just kind of is
关于事物而且它只是一种
back and forth so communication comes to
来回让沟通来
an end when these stresses well when you
当你这些压力很大的时候结束了
you're focused on ministry she's focused
你专注于她专注的事工
on what's going on at home
关于在家里发生了什么
communication has a tendency to come to
通信有一种倾向来
an end and you you shut down you
结束，你关闭了你
withdraw potentially she withdraws okay
有可能她退出了
all right well you also mark
好吧，你也标记
perfectionism here and you also talk
完美主义在这里，你也谈
about your physical relationship in
关于你的身体关系
marriage your sexual relationship and
婚姻你的性关系和
why did you mark that as
为什么你把它标记为
part of the problem here well I I think
这里问题的一部分很好，我认为
just the desire that obviously is
只是显然是欲望
probably more apparent in a man instead
在一个男人中可能更明显
you know versus a woman as far as for
你知道对一个女人只要 对
that sexual need to be met mm-hmm
性需要得到满足mm-hmm
you know there's that desire to be met
你知道有必须满足这种愿望
you know even on a weekly basis at times
你有时甚至每周都知道
or a couple times a week and when she is
或者每周几次，当她是
exhausted coming home from her teaching
从她的教学中回到家里疲惫不堪
at the school and just tired from being
在学校，只是厌倦了
with the kids all day and just wants to
与孩子们一整天，只是想
put her feet up and take a nap and go to
站起来小睡，然后去
sleep and I come back from the church
睡觉，我从教堂回来
and I've been sedentary most of the day
我大部分时间都久坐不动
and I want to get up and go play and I
我想起床去玩我
want to enjoy her and I want to talk and
想要享受她，我想和她说话
and she she wants to have nothing to do
而她，她想要什么都没有做
with that she just wants to flip on a
因为她只是想翻转一下
movie or or go to bed and she's too
电影或者去睡觉，她也是
tired to really enjoy any times like
很累，真的很享受任何时候喜欢
that and so we've tried to talk to you
那个，所以我们试着跟你说话
that we've tried to to think about when
我们试图考虑什么时候
would be the best time because you know
因为你知道，这将是最好的时间
I know her heart and her heart desires
我知道她的心和她的心愿
to please me and I want to honor her and
取悦我， 我想尊重她和
not be you know so selfish where I have
我不知道你在哪里这么自私
to have this and have all the time but
有这个，并有所有的时间但是
at the same time it's a biblical desire
同时它是一个圣经的愿望
that God has given to both of us to to
上帝给了我们两个人 对
what we have and we want to meet that in
我们拥有什么，我们希望在那里遇到什么
one another but I think just the the way
彼此，但我认为就是这样
our lives are going in two different
我们的生活有两种不同
directions
方向
and it's just hard to meet at that that
并且很难见到那一点
time we'll do where this can happen on a
时间我们会做到这一点
consistent basis and because of that I I
一致的基础，因为那个II
have a hard time getting to sleep
有一个很难入睡
sometimes we just go to bed and and I
有时我们只是去睡觉而且我
can't get to sleep because I know I've
无法入睡，因为我知道我已经
been denied that satisfaction and she's
被拒绝满意而且她是
just you know gone to sleep on me and I
只是你知道我和我睡觉了
haven't been excited to talk about the
谈论这个问题 并没有兴奋
day or some counseling sessions I've
我有一天或一些咨询会议
gone through or enjoy that and I've just
通过或享受，我只是
gotten up and gone read but it's so hard
起床后不读了但是很难
to focus I just anger sets in and just
专注于我只是愤怒和刚才
frustration at why why she unwilling to
沮丧为什么她不愿意
do this and it just is like a spiral
做到这一点就像螺旋一样
downward
向下
in my thoughts and it takes a while just
在我的想法中，它需要一段时间
to weigh that before the Lord and so
在主之前权衡这一点
that's that's a definite struggle that
那是一场明确的斗争
we're going through okay I mean what
我们正在经历好吧我的意思是什么
you're sharing is really helpful and I
你分享的确非常有帮助而且我
want you to know that at least some of
希望你至少知道一些
the pressures that you're facing as a
你面临 的压力
couple this is not unusual times and at
这对夫妇来说并不是不寻常的时间
some particular point even you as a
甚至你作为一个特别的观点
pastor me realize this the more you are
牧师我越了解你
involved with your flock and attempt to
参与你的羊群并尝试
help them you'll find out that this is
帮助他们，你会发现，这是
not unusual when a couple has struggles
当一对夫妇挣扎时并不罕见
like you're facing it will hurt their
就像你面对它会伤害他们
physical relationship with one another
彼此的身体关系
now God has answers for that and I think
现在上帝有这个答案，我想
that you'll see you'll see why I'm
你会看到你会明白为什么我
saying that as we progress now we ask
说我们现在正在进步，我们会问
you a couple of questions and Joe this
你几个问题和乔本
is the way in which you answered them
是你回答他们的方式
what is what is your problem what is it
什么是什么是你的问题是什么 呢
that brings you here and you said my
带你到这里，你说我的
wife seems to be withdrawing for me I
妻子似乎在为我退缩了
don't know how to keep her or to help
不知道如何保持她或帮助
her with her depression I'm really
她的抑郁症我真的
worried about her is there anything that
担心她有什么
you want to add to that help me to
你想添加到那帮助我
understand it I think just approaching
了解它我认为刚刚接近
this you know spiritually there there's
你在灵性上知道那里有
definitely physical things that I see as
绝对是我认为的物质事物
far as just sleeping more than the
就像只是睡觉一样
normal just is undisciplined with her
正常只是与她无纪律
with her time as far as going to bed
和她一起睡觉的时间
early and waking up as late as possible
早醒来尽可能晚
we have talked a number of times about
我们已经谈过很多次了
the importance of spending you know
花钱你知道的重要性
devotional time together and I wake up
在一起的灵修时间和我醒来
very early deal they have my own quiet
非常早的交易他们有我自己的安静
time with the Lord and my desire and I
与主同在的时间和我的愿望
know it's hers at least she expresses
至少她知道这是她的表达
that to me is to spend that time with me
这对我来说这些时间与我
in prayer before the day and whatnot but
在白天之前的祈祷和诸如此类的东西
when it you know we get down to the
当你知道我们得到了
bottom of it she doesn't want to wake up
在她的底部，她不想醒来
in the morning she doesn't want to give
早上她不想给
me that time she would much rather have
我那个时候她宁愿拥有
her own time in bed
她在床上的时间
and she wakes up just and even kind of
她只是甚至有种 并唤醒
Angry as far as why I would want to
愤怒至于为什么我会想
insist this upon her this early so it's
这个早就坚持这个，所以它就是这样
kind of like duplicitous have heard it
有点像两面派听过的
you know to to be saying that and then
你知道在说，然后
to not have any desire for that when you
当你没有任何欲望
know that's something that we'd like to
知道这 是我们想要 的东西
to develop in our lives and I think that
在我们的生活中发展，我认为
spiritual component is so important to
精神成分是如此重要
having a healthy relationship and I see
我看到了一段健康的关系
what's happened when that has gone down
发生了什么事情发生了变化
we're not spending the prayer time that
我们不是在那里度过祈祷时间
I feel we need to spend together I feel
我觉得我们需要一起度过
like it's affected her personal
喜欢它影响了她的个人
devotional life with the Lord as far as
与主的奉献生活
you know she's she's been in the she's
你知道她是她一直在她身边
been in the word but she talks to me
一直在说，但她跟我说话
like she has never even you know studied
就像她从来没有你知道研究过
the Bible recently just the way she acts
最近圣经就是她行事的方式
and behaves or doesn't seem to be any
并且表现或似乎不是任何
connection there of a biblical truth and
与圣经真相的联系
how she's living her life on discipline
她是如何依靠纪律生活的
just over sleeping anger and even just a
只是沉睡，甚至只是一个
overwhelming sadness and a sense of kind
压倒性的悲伤和善良的感觉
of loathsome somberness that look it is
看起来是令人讨厌的忧郁
just hard to understand when the you
只是很难理解当你
know just read the Psalms and you can be
知道刚刚阅读诗篇， 你可以
so encouraged and and and I think it's
所以鼓励和我认为是
just really I don't know what to do you
只是我真的不知道该怎么做你
know we've tried a number of different
知道我们尝试了很多不同的东西
things I've tried to get her some some
我试图让她得到一些东西
counseling from one of the elders why is
其中一位长老的咨询原因是
in our church and and that lasted for a
在我们的教堂里，并持续了一个
few weeks and you know maybe some
几个星期，你知道也许一些
helpful things came out of that just
有用的东西就出来了，只是
another friend in the church but she's
教堂里的另一位朋友，但她是
still the same there hasn't seem to be
还是一样也似乎有不 被
any real substantial change that has
任何真正的重大变化
been continuous it's been just little
一直持续它只是一点点
bits and pieces there but it's always
那里的点点滴滴，但总是如此
been reverting back into the same
已恢复回相同
patterns
模式
Joe I need to ask you this question and
乔，我需要问你这个问题
I don't want you to answer it twice well
我不想让你回答这个问题以及两次
what's the word I want to use I don't
我想要使用的是什么，我不知道
want you to answer it
希望你回答它
real quickly without thought but do you
真的很快没有想到，但你呢
really love Julie yeah she is
真的很喜欢朱莉，是的
she was my joy she's the one that I
她是我的喜悦， 她就是我
think about constantly and since the
从头开始思考
first day I said eyes upon her she was
第一天，我说她是她的眼睛
the girl of my dreams that if had the
我梦想中的女孩，如果有的话
qualities that I wanted to seeing my
我希望看到我的 品质
wife yeah and you know at the same time
老婆， 是的，你知道的同时
I I have to admit that just the great
我必须承认，只有伟大的
responsibilities in ministry and and
在事工和职责中的责任
caring for her sometimes can sometimes
有时可以照顾她
can muffle that kind of expression of
可以马弗那种表达的
love that I really desire to show her at
喜欢我真的希望向她展示
times and the kind of care and
时间和那种关怀和
compassion that I think are important
我认为同情很重要
there and I'm still I feel like this is
那里，我仍然觉得这是
more for me in some ways because I'm
在某些方面对我来说更多，因为我
struggling really with how to you know
我真的很挣扎着你怎么知道
how to handle my own yeah sense of
如何处理我自己的感觉
responsibility and and unworthiness and
责任和不配
discipline and part of me is what I'm
纪律和我的一部分就是我
studying I feel like I'm neglecting her
学习我觉得我忽略了她
because I'm not spending time with her
因为我没有和她在一起
and when I'm spending time with her I
当我和她在一起时，我
feel this tension of life should be
感受到生活的紧张应该是
preparing for my next sermon or
准备我的下一篇布道或
preparing for next counselling session
准备下一次咨询会议
and there's this constant battle back
这是不断的反击
and forth and and my desires to honor
我的愿望和荣誉
her my desires to really like Ephesians
她渴望真正喜欢以弗所书
5 to lay my life down for her in
5为我的生命奠定了基础
whatever way that I can and that's one
无论我能做什么，那就是一个
of the reasons why I wanted to come here
我想来这里的原因
to speak with you because I think it's
和你说话因为我认为是
reached that level where we need some
达到了我们需要的水平
substantial health and and I do mm-hmm
健康，我做mm-嗯
well you know how Jesus asked Peter not
嗯，你知道耶稣不怎么问彼得
just once but three times and Peter do
只有一次，但三次，彼得
you really love me and one of the
你真的爱我的一个
reasons why I asked you that question
我问你这个问题的原因
this particular point is even if Julie
尤其是朱莉
doesn't perform the way that you think
没有按照你的想法行事
that she should perform is that the
她应该表演的是
gauge or it's at the measure of whether
衡量或衡量是否
or not you're going to love her you know
或不是你会爱她，你知道
I think that's something that you're
我认为那是你的事
going to
即将
to to work on and and and struggle with
努力工作和与之斗争
I want to really come back and talk
我想真的回来谈谈
about that a little bit later on so
关于那稍后的事情
doctors regathered extensive data from
医生们从中收集了大量数据
Joe in that segment you're all a very
Joe在那个片段你是一个非常好的人
observant group you you observed a lot
你观察了很多观察小组
of things you're good you observed a lot
你看到很多很好的东西
in Joe and also there's a lot to observe
在Joe ，还有很多值得观察的地方
in John and how he's gathering data and
约翰以及他如何收集数据和
how he's counseling and also we observe
他是如何辅导的，也是我们观察的
some things from Julie as well in this
朱莉的一些东西也在这里
very next segment which is also in the
第二天段， 这也是在
first session that they're meeting
他们正在开会的第一次会议
together we're going to see dr. Street
我们一起 去见博士。街
gathering information from Julie okay
收集朱莉的信息好吧
now and some of the problem checklist
现在和一些问题清单
things you just about covered the gamut
你刚才所涉及的事情涵盖了整个范围
here so you check several things that
在这里你要检查几件事
are listed here you one of the first
在这里列出你的第一个
things you put on here was anger can you
你放在这里的东西是你的愤怒
tell me a little bit about that well I
我告诉我一点点
think it started more with just kind of
认为它开始更多的只是一种
confusion and apathy a little bit and um
混淆和冷漠一点点嗯
I'm angry yet well where to start um I
我很生气， 但是我从哪里开始
think I'm most I'm very angry at myself
我想我最开心的就是对自己很生气
because I I mean I know what I'm I think
因为我的意思是我知道我在想什么
I know that I'm supposed to be doing
我知道我应该这样做
what my role is and um it just felt like
我的角色是什么，而且感觉就像
oh there's an inability to perform it
哦，无法执行它
and um you know I'm convicted about
而且你知道我被判有罪
things and um you know I
事情，嗯，你知道我
I don't you noticed in my role as a
我没注意到我的角色
pastor like I just like him and
牧师就像我喜欢他一样
following John in the harness um but
跟随约翰在线束，但是
with it without the ability to really
没有真正的能力
you know if that change so it's kind of
你知道这种变化是否有所改变
frustrating and I get mad at myself is
令人沮丧，我对自己生气了
why can't I just pull myself together
为什么我不能把自己拉到一起
and you know I know the truth I
而你知道我知道真相
graduated from Bible College a girl a
毕业于圣经学院的女生a
Christian home I've always been in the
基督徒家我一直都在
church and um so it's like I know the
教堂和嗯所以就像我知道的那样
truth is just getting there to apply it
真相只是到那里来应用它
and I'm I mean Joel alluded to this too
而我就是说Joel也提到了这一点
but just angry it
但是生气了
frustrated at the ministry and it's
这个部门很沮丧
different that I thought it would be and
不同的是我认为它会和
he's gone an awful lot and I think he
他走得太厉害了，我想他
has unfair expectations and so are you
有不公平的期望，你也是
have you or been it's safe for me to say
你有没有安全的说法
I don't want to put words in your mouth
我不想把话放在嘴里
that you've been angry Joe - mmhmm yeah
你生气了乔 -嗯，是的
I think I mean that comes and goes I
我想，我的意思是来得快，去我
don't think I'm constantly furious at
不要以为我一直都很生气
him but um it's easy for me to he's he
他，但UM很容易对我来说，他是他
can be inconsiderate and um sometimes I
可能是不体贴的， 有时我
want him to show me the kind of um
希望他能告诉我那种嗯
affection that he shows his congregation
他向他的会众表达的感情
you know if I was someone in the church
你知道我是否是教会里的某个人
that you should show me that same grace
你应该向我展示同样的恩典
um or more so I'm really good that's
嗯以上 ，所以我真的好这
alright that's reason why we put these
好吧，这就是为什么我们把这些
out by the way don't you know that um
顺便问一下你不知道那个嗯
okay good um I'm it's not good that it's
好的嗯，我是不是很好
happening here but it's what you're
发生在这里，但这就是你的意思
sharing with me is helpful then you also
与我分享对你有帮助
Mark anxiety as Joe did um what would
标记焦虑，乔做了什么会
you say can you help me with this um Oh
你说能帮助我吗哦哦
honestly like I don't think I'm acting
老实说，我不认为我在表演
like a believer and sometimes there's
像信徒一样，有时甚至是信徒
anxiety there that I mean I know the
那里的焦虑，我的意思是我知道
truth and I've seen fruit my wife in the
真相，我看到了我妻子的果实
past and doesn't seem to be a lot there
过去，似乎并没有那么多
and I don't want to just put it on you
而且我不想只是把它放在你身上
know I'm not to fabricate something if
知道如果，我不会制造一些东西
that's not true so that kind of this
这不是真的所以这样
thing it makes you anxious sure and you
让你焦虑的事情和你
know if you're going through a severe
知道你是否经历过严重的
emotional upset
情绪不安
the way you are going through now it's
你现在正在经历的方式
not unusual that a person begins to
不寻常的是一个人 开始
question their own walk with the Lord
质疑他们自己与主同行
their own salvation that's not unusual
他们自己的救赎并不罕见
at all and actually if I can kind of
在所有的情况下，如果我可以的话
interject at this particular point I
插入这一特定点我
don't think that we should view that as
不要以为我们应该将其视为
a negative thing I think that God would
一个消极的事我认为上帝会
have us use times like this that's one
让我们使用像这样的时间
of the actual upsides if I can use that
如果我可以使用它的实际好处
terminology of a time like this of you
像你这样的时间的术语
being able to examine where do I stand
能够检查我的立场
with the Lord weird already really
与主怪异已经真的
staying with him do I really trust him
和他在一起我真的相信他
so all right I appreciate your honesty
所以没事我很欣赏你的诚实
there anything else in terms of anxiety
还有什么焦虑条款
well I mean obviously I don't know it's
好吧，我的意思是显然我不知道它
all mumbled up but about being a parent
所有人都嘟,,但是关于做父母
that what kind of a mom in my kevie
在我的kevie中 ，这是一个 什么样的妈妈
uh-huh so yeah absolutely especially
嗯所以是绝对特别是
with this new responsibility staring you
这个新责任盯着你
in the face and all of a sudden now
现在突然面对现实
you're struggling with something that
你的东西是挣扎
has not really happened and any severity
没有真正发生过任何严重性
in the past in your life just yeah
你过去的生活只是耶
anxious about the future and decisions
对未来和决定感到焦虑
Joe makes and wherever going isn't a
乔制造，无论走到哪里都不是
family and a church and I don't know
家庭和教堂，我不知道
just it's all kind of mumbled together
只是它有点笨拙地混在一起
okay
好的
all right then you also put apathy hmm
好吧那你也冷漠了
um yeah I just I feel like I've lost
恩，是的，我只是感觉自己已经迷失了
interesting in life that's kind of like
生活中有趣的有点像
on a practical level I do the dishes
在实际水平上我做菜
they're just going to be there again
他们只会再去那里
yeah like I haven't actually in the past
是的，我实际上并没有过去
couple and this is just this is not like
情侣这就是这个不喜欢
you know this is not like her in a lot
你知道这不是很多她
of ways as far as how we started out our
就我们如何开始我们的方式而言
marriage I mean this has just been
婚姻我的意思是刚才
recently in the last within a you know a
最近在最后一个你知道了
couple years or so things have just
事情刚好几年左右
slowly started to digress and yet the
慢慢地开始离题了
first few years of our marriage it was
最初几年， 我们的婚姻是
just there in seminary together it was
就在神学院那里
my desire that you know these would be
我希望你知道这些
the best years of our life and the
我们生命中最美好的时光
preparatory for the ministry and we were
为我们事工做准备
enjoying things and I would hear the
享受的东西，我会听到
horror stories of pastors out there
那里牧师的恐怖故事
where is the burdens and the weight of
负担在哪里，重量在哪里
ministry and all the responsibilities
事工和所有责任
and wife's responsibilities that they
和他们的妻子的责任
conflicted at times or they they had a
有时会发生冲突，或者他们有过冲突
tough time meeting each other and and
艰难的时刻相遇和
there was one story where the the
有一个故事，其中的
husband came home from work and the wife
丈夫下班回家和妻子
had all of his books on the bed with a
把他所有的书都放在床上
note saying I'm gone you can sleep with
字条说我走了，你可以睡
your books and you hear these stories
你的书，你听到这些故事
and just grieves you again and you know
再次让你伤心，你知道
that your wife you know you've seen her
你的妻子，你知道你见过她
joyful about the minister you know her
对你了解她的部长感到高兴
hard and and you've experienced a
很难， 你经历过一次
wonderful love relationship and to see
美好的爱情关系和看到
things digress like that you just it
事情离你喜欢它
can't help but but make me weep and
忍不住让我哭泣
mourn over over her because I I'm to
为她而哀悼， 因为我要
present her at one day before the Lord
在主 面前的一天献上她
is this is you know this is who she to
这是你知道她是谁
be married to knows to Christ and to
结婚，要知道基督和
present her perfect and blameless before
在此之前表现出完美和无可指责
him
他
and this just doesn't seem like this is
而这似乎并不 喜欢这
the woman that I married in a lot of
我在很多已婚 女人
ways um it doesn't seem like I mean it's
这些方式似乎不是我的意思
not the person I was either cuz I'm
我不是那个人，因为我是
right on top of it right all right all
权在它右上方没事
right there's so many things that you've
你有很多事情
listed here on the problem checklist I
列在此处的问题清单我
know that in a future session I'm going
我知道在未来的会议中我会去
to come back and talk with you a little
回来和你谈谈一下
bit about some of this for instance you
一些有关此比如你一点
talked about you've had a loss of
谈到你已经失去了
appetite which is also common with real
食欲也很普遍
severe depression you talked about
你谈到了严重的抑郁症
changing lifestyle communication as well
改变生活方式的沟通
conflicts of course you Mark depression
冲突当然是马克沮丧
and fear and guilt loneliness memory
和恐惧和内疚的孤独记忆
some case your memories fuzzy or lost is
在某些情况下，你的记忆模糊或丢失了
that what you mean by that I just I
这就是你的意思，我只是我
think it goes along with just it's hard
认为它同意它很难
to concentrate and then just like yeah
集中精力然后就像是的
you're kind of living in a fog yeah yeah
你有点生活在雾中是的
of course moodiness and then like Joe
当然情绪低落，然后像乔
you talk about sexual relationship and
你谈论性关系和
are and then sleep a lot a lot okay is
是的，然后睡了很多好
the sleep good when you sleep or is it
你睡觉时睡眠好还是睡觉呢
restless isn't it that's why I keep
不安的不是这就是我保持的原因
sleeping yeah yeah all right
睡觉是啊好吧
so we ask you the same questions here
所以我们在这里问你同样的问题
what is the problem I've been struggling
我一直在努力的问题是什么？
with severe depression because of my
由于我的严重抑郁症
relationship with my husband mm-hmm I
与我丈夫的 关系mm-hmm我
feel like that we're drifting further
我觉得我们正在进一步漂移
and further apart and then he doesn't
并进一步分开，然后他没有
understand me in my needs I also feel
在我的需要中了解我，我也觉得
guilty because I can't get things done
因为我无法完成任务而感到内疚
around the house hey what else would you
周围的房子，嘿，你还有什么会
like to add to that I just feels like
喜欢添加到我感觉就像
it's a cycle of I can't I can't meet any
这是一个我无法满足的循环
expectations I don't eat my own I don't
期望我不吃我自己的我不
meet the role of a wife I don't meet the
遇到妻子的角色我不符合
expectations of the church I just in and
教会的期望我只是在和
it's like you're just stuck I can't I
就像你被困住了我不能
can't um what's the word kind of jump
不能用什么词来跳跃
start you know I can't jump start
开始你知道我不能跳起来
myself out of that uh um it's like yeah
我自己出的那个呃嗯这就像耶
I have good intentions when I go to bed
我上床睡觉时心情很好
at night have I'm gonna get up and I'm
晚上我会起床而且我会
gonna do these while I did at the
会做这些，而我在做
beginning um I'm gonna get up and I'm
开始嗯我会起床而且我是
gonna start my date like Joe wants me to
要像Joe想要的那样开始约会
and we're gonna um be on top of it all
我们会在这一切之上
day and but I'm just so exhausted and so
那一天，但我已经筋疲力尽了
it's gotten worse since I've been
自从我去以后它变得更糟
pregnant obviously so it's hard to know
怀孕显然很难知道
what pregnancy and what's yeah the for
什么怀孕，什么是耶
pregnancy and you know I was always
怀孕，你知道我永远
brought up not to make excuses and such
提出不要找借口等
try not to but I mean there's something
尽量不要，但我的意思是有一些东西
that's well you know keeping me from my
那就是你知道让我远离我的
good intentions and then lately I just I
善意，最近我只是我
don't really even have good intentions
真的没有好意
Dantas don't you don't want to try
Dantas你不想尝试
alright we got a lot more information
好吧，我们得到了更多的信息
right there didn't we picture for a
就在那里，我们没有想到的
minute being John Street sitting there
约翰街坐在那里
there's a lot going on you've got the
有很多事情你已经得到了
biblical counsellor simultaneously
圣经辅导员同时
gathering this information and also
收集这些信息也
thinking through how the Scriptures
思考圣经如何
apply to each person and to each bit of
适用于每个人，并的每一位
information that he's hearing the
他听到的信息
biblical counsellor is also caring for
圣经辅导员也在关心
each person with a christ-like love as
每个人都像基督一样的爱
they're sitting there hearing the story
他们坐在那里听故事
about what's going on in these lives and
关于这些生活中发生的事情
in the marriage well in the next clip
在下一个剪辑的婚姻中
and this one is also from the first
这个也是第一个
session John Street councils Joe and
会议约翰街议会乔和
Julie regarding depression because
朱莉因为抑郁症
everybody is down at different points in
每个人都在不同的地方
life there are times where you're
生活中有时候你会
excited and you're happy and things seem
兴奋， 你很高兴，事情似乎
to be going your way and you're joyful
走你的路，你很快乐
in life you feel blessed and then there
在生活中，你感到幸福，然后在那里
are times where you just feel down you
是你感到沮丧的时候
don't feel on top of the world
不觉得在 世界之巅
and usually those time times occur to me
通常那些时间都发生在我身上
every day when I have to roll out of bed
每天，当我要滚下了床
early in the morning I feel that that's
一大早我觉得那就是
one of the last things I want to do is
我想做的最后一件事是
get out of bed mm-hmm okay
下床mm-hmm没关系
but if we were to in a sense sum up all
但如果我们在某种意义上总结一切
the biblical ideas of what depression is
关于抑郁症的圣经观念
the way in which the contemporary world
当代世界的方式
describes all the symptoms of depression
描述了抑郁症的所有症状
that go on we would say this that
继续我们会这样说
depression is being down and out that
抑郁症正在逐渐消失
does equal depression being down and out
确实是平等的抑郁症
now what's the difference between the
现在有什么区别了
two well the difference between the two
两个很好的两者之间的区别
in this one this is your feelings and
在这一个，这是你的感受和
this other one your feelings now are
这另外一个你的感情现在
determining what you do okay
确定你做什么没关系
this is just feeling low that's what it
这只是感觉很低，这就是它
is
是
this is feeling low and I believe that
感觉很低，我相信
there are some people that are given and
有一些人被给予和
sometimes different stages of life like
有时不同的生活阶段就像
a unique stage of life that you're going
你要去的独特生活阶段
through this particular time some people
有些人通过这个特定的时间
are given more to feeling low than other
比其他人感觉更低
people some people have to struggle with
人们有的人 有斗争
this more than other people do maybe
这比其他人做得更多
it's part of the the weaknesses of the
它是这个弱点的一部分
way in which God has created them but
上帝创造他们的方式但是
being down and out this is more than
沮丧和沮丧这不仅仅是
just feeling that low now I'm beginning
我现在感觉很低落
to ignore responsibilities i i'm not
忽视责任我不是
fulfilling
履行
I should say not for fill a filling put
我应该说不是填馅放
that in there I'm not fulfilling what
在那里，我没有实现什么
God wants me to do now we know that
上帝希望我现在知道这一点
there are certain types of diseases and
有某些类型的疾病和
circumstances that can bring on feelings
可以在感受带给情况
of depression symptoms of depression but
抑郁症的症状，但
all of those types of problems are
所有这些类型的问题都是
easily discernible with a good thorough
通过良好的彻底很容易辨别
physical we know that and that's one of
物理我们知道那是那个
the reasons why I asked you the question
我问你这个问题的原因
Julie whether or not the psychiatrist
朱莉是否精神科医生
had done anything other than ask you
除了问你之外什么都做了
questions whether they had actually
问他们是否真的
taken you through any specific tests now
现在带你完成任何特定的测试
I'm going to assume obviously that your
我明显会假设你的
OBGYN has done that in other words they
OBGYN换句话说就是他们
usually are pretty thorough and trying
通常是非常彻底和尝试
to help you with your pregnancy making
帮助你做怀孕
sure that you're healthy the baby's
确定你的宝宝很健康
healthy and let's assume that all the
健康，让我们假设所有的
blood tests and everything that the
血液测试和一切
OBGYN has given you has turned out well
OBGYN给你的结果很好
I mean there's no sign of any organic
我的意思是没有任何有机的迹象
abnormalities as going on in you well it
在你身上发生异常
probably wouldn't hurt and I could
可能不会受伤，我可以
probably encourage you to go and problem
可能会鼓励你去问题
and get a thoroughgoing physical again
并再次获得彻底的身体
just to rule out any possibilities and
只是为了排除任何可能性
that's something that you could talk
这是你可以说的话
about between the two of you but if the
在你们两个之间，但如果是
OBGYN is jumped out a thorough job then
那时OBGYN跳出了彻底的工作
we can say that this is not organically
我们可以说这不是有机的
caused the etiology of this or the very
引起这种或非常的病因
core of this causes of the problem is
这个问题的核心原因是
not an organic issue it doesn't have to
它不是一个有机的问题
do with Julie's physiological body other
做朱莉的生理身体其他
than the fact that you're going through
而不是你正在经历的事实
normal changes with pregnancy a lot of
怀孕的正常变化很多
the changes going on in your life but
你生活中正在发生的变化
even prior to this this is more of a
甚至在此之前，这更像是一个
type of depression that is is that you
抑郁症是一种类型是你
things have changed in your life
你生活中的一切都发生了变化
radically changed it's changed in Joe's
从根本上改变了乔的改变
life and how are the two of you
生活，你们两个怎么样
addressing that change how are you
解决那个改变你的方式
dealing with that so I want you to think
处理那个，所以我想让你思考
about this that there's a difference
关于这一点，这是有区别的
between being down and being down and
是下来，趴下之间
out one is you just feel low but you
一个是你只是觉得低，但你
continue to function you continue to do
继续运作你继续做
what God wants you to do all right and
上帝希望你做的一切都好
even though you may feel low and you may
即使你可能感觉自己很低落
feel down for weeks and months a person
一个人感觉几周和几个月
continues to do what God wants them to
继续做神希望他们
do this is where a person has totally
这是一个人完全的地方
given in and saying all right I give up
放弃并说好，我放弃了
I don't care anymore in some cases a
在某些情况下，我不在乎了
person like this contemplates suicide or
这样的人考虑自杀或
maybe they may curl up in their bed in a
也许他们可以在他们的床上蜷缩在
fetal position and not want to get out
胎位并不想出去
of bed ever that's when you're down and
床当你失意过这和
out now that's true depression and it
现在这是真正的沮丧和它
sounds like to me from what Julie is
听起来像朱莉的样子
described when Joe is described about
描述乔的描述
her life she's coming close to this and
她的生活她正在接近这个和
probably even has given in to this in
甚至可能已经屈服于此了
some cases all right not fulfilling what
有些情况下还没有完成什么
God wants you to do well after what we
上帝希望你在我们之后做得好
just saw in session number one dr.
刚刚在第一场比赛中看到了博士。
Street assigned homework from the
街分配作业 从
scriptures Joe and Julie both did their
经文乔和朱莉都做了他们的
homework from the scriptures and then
然后从经文中做作业
they all met together again for sessions
他们都聚在一起参加会议
two and three in our next section of
我们下一节中的两个和三个
film which is the last one we'll see
我们将看到 的最后一部电影
today we're going to see the counselors
今天我们要去看辅导员
comments prior to session number four
第四场会议之前的评论
he's just going to talk to us about the
他只是要 我们谈谈对
case followed by the first 15 minutes of
案件紧接着前15分钟
session for what happens next let's
会话会发生什么接下来我们
watch we have been dealing with clinical
看我们一直在处理临床问题
depression in this particular series on
抑郁症在这个特殊的系列上
counseling those who are depressed you
辅导那些谁是你郁闷
probably by now had the opportunity to
可能到现在有机会
watch our first DVD which was the first
观看我们的第一张DVD
counseling appointment that we had with
咨询我们的约会
Joe and Julie
乔和朱莉
you can tell that Joe himself is very
你可以说乔本人非常
much a perfectionist he wants to do well
他想做得很好的完美主义者
in his ministry in and of itself wanting
在他自己的事工本身中
to do well is not bad but this has
做得好也不错，但这有
affected Joe's relationship to Julie and
影响乔与朱莉和朱莉的关系
Julie can tell it in fact it's affected
事实上，朱莉可以说它受到了影响
her quite a bit Julie herself has really
她有点朱莉自己真的
sir come to depression this brings us to
先生来到抑郁症这带来了我们
our fourth counseling appointment with
我们的第四次咨询预约
them and over the past second and third
他们和过去的第二和第三
counseling appointments things were kind
咨询约会事情是善良的
of rocky but slowly I believe both Joe
岩石但慢慢地我相信乔
and Julie are beginning to realize that
朱莉开始意识到这一点
there really is hope in doing things
真的是在做事情的希望
God's Way
上帝的道路
Julie's beginning to understand what we
朱莉开始明白我们是什么
talked about in the very first session
在第一次会议上谈到
about the importance of joy flowing out
关于快乐流出的重要性
of obedience and so we're excited about
服从，所以我们很兴奋
that in this particular session I really
在这个特定的会议中，我真的
want to work with Joe on him in
想与乔 在他的工作
relationship to his being more gentle
与他的关系更温柔
and understanding with Julie helping her
与朱莉帮助她的理解
and yet at the same time not feeding her
但同时却没有喂她
self-pity and I want to work with Julie
自怜，我想和朱莉一起工作
in relationship to her fully
与她完全相关
understanding getting a better grasp
理解得到更好的掌握
from the Word of God about how God deals
从上帝的话语中了解上帝如何处理
with depression and how God wants her to
抑郁症和上帝希望她如何
respond to his word so that she doesn't
回应他的话，以便她不这样做
succumb to depression as readily as she
像她一样容易屈服于抑郁症
has in the past overall I've been very
我过去总体上一直非常
pleased with their progress they are a
对他们的进步很满意他们是一个
couple that demonstrates that they want
表明他们想要的夫妇
to work hard on this particular problem
努力解决这个特殊问题
and they have a lot of motivation to do
和他们有很大的动力做
that even though julie has struggled
即使朱莉一直在努力
sometimes she's failed some sometimes
有时候她有些失败了
she has given in to her feelings and
她已经屈服于她的感受和
resorted back into irresponsibility not
不再采取不负责任的态度
fulfilling her responsibilities around
围绕履行她的职责
the home and of course as she grows in
家里，当然还有她成长的地方
terms of her pregnancy this is going to
这是她的怀孕条款
even be magnified even worse and many of
甚至被放大甚至更糟和许多
you have probably heard of post Parden
你可能听说过Parden
depression
萧条
I'm and what really happens there is
我和那里真正发生了什么
that there's a major physiological
这是一个重要的生理问题
change in a woman and with a depression
改变一个女人和抑郁症
that she's already experiencing than
她已经体验过了
this on top of it it's probably a good
这在它的上面它可能是一个很好的
thing that we're really grounding and
我们真正的基础和事情
rooting her in the Word of God which
使她成为上帝的话语
ultimately is her hope and that they're
最终是她的希望，他们是
working on this problem together the
在这个问题上一起工作的
fact that she's getting into Scripture
事实上，她正在进入圣经
studying it understanding what it has to
研究它了解它有什么
say about not just being down but being
说的不只是被下来，但被
down and out and understanding the
潦倒和理解
anatomy of her own depression and the
解剖她自己的抑郁症和
fact that her husband is willing to work
事实上，她的丈夫是愿意工作
with her all of that has been an
她所有的已经是一个
encouragement as she is evidencing what
鼓励，因为她在证明什么
we talked about if you remember in our
我们谈过你是否记得我们的
first counseling appointment in Romans
在罗马人的第一次咨询预约
chapter 15 and verse 4 through
第15章和第4节到第4节
perseverance and encouragement of
坚持不懈和鼓励
Scripture perseverance is really what
圣经的毅力才是真正的
Julie needs to understand here so as we
就像我们一样，朱莉需要在这里理解
get into this particular session I want
进入我想要的这个特定会议
you to watch carefully the way in which
你要仔细观察它的方式
we work with Julie in terms of helping
我们在帮助方面与朱莉合作
her see the core issues of her problem
她看到了她问题的核心问题
especially what's going on in her heart
尤其是她心中正在发生的事情
so let's get into our session
所以让我们进入我们的会议
well welcome Joe and Julie it's good to
非常欢迎Joe和Julie，这很好
have you back again well I can't believe
让你再次回来我不敢相信
already four weeks have gone by and and
已经有四星期过去了，和
to see what God is doing in your life is
看什么神正在做你的生活
a great encouragement we want to begin
我们想要开始的巨大鼓励
again with prayer so let's get started
再次祈祷所以让我们开始吧
and just dive into your homework and
然后潜入你的作业和
talk a little about what God is teaching
谈谈上帝在教什么
you there okay gracious father we are
你们， 我们是好亲切的父亲
grateful that your love for us is
感激你对我们的爱
demonstrated especially in your
特别在你的
faithfulness and we know father that you
忠诚，我们知道父亲，你
are always a faithful God and then we
永远是忠诚的上帝，然后是我们
have a constant intercessor by the name
这个名字有一个不变的代祷者
of Jesus Christ two intercessors is our
耶稣基督的两个代祷是我们的
high priest before you intercedes for us
在你为我们代求之前，大祭司
and father we would ask for his help and
和父亲，我们会请求他的帮助和
the work of the Holy Spirit in our lives
圣灵在我们生命中的工作
during this session today I pray you
在今天这个会议期间， 我祈祷你
help Joe as he attempts to be a godly
帮助乔，因为他试图成为一个敬虔的人
husband and a godly pastor and in the
丈夫和一位敬虔的牧师
future a godly father and I would pray
未来是一个敬虔的父亲，我会祈祷
father the same that you would be of
父亲一样，你会成为
help to Julie as well as she seeks to be
帮助朱莉以及她的目的是
a godly woman a godly wife and as well
一个敬虔的女人，一个敬虔的妻子，以及
as a godly pastor's wife this we pray in
作为一位敬虔的牧师的妻子， 我们祈祷
Christ's name Amen
基督的名字阿门
well we concluded our last session and
以及我们结束了最后一次会议和
and I felt that that last session we
我觉得我们上次会议
made a lot of progress and especially
取得了很大的进步，特别是
with Julie and Julie it's good to see
与朱莉和朱莉一起，很高兴看到
you a little bit more optimism than our
你比我们更乐观一点
earlier sessions even though I know it's
早期的会议， 即使我知道它
been hard for you I'm happy that God is
一直用心为您服务我很高兴，神
really working in your life and Joe
真的在你的生活和乔工作
you're beginning to understand too I
你也开始理解我了
think what needs to happen in terms of
想想需要发生什么
being a caring and loving husband and
作为一个充满爱心和爱心的丈夫
coming alongside Julie and during these
与朱莉并肩作战期间
times like I want you to grab your Bible
好像我希望你抓住你的圣经
just before we get to our homework and I
就在我们完成作业之前和我
want you to go over to first Peter
希望你去第一个彼得
chapter three just for a moment
第三章只是片刻
Joe this is especially for you first
乔，这是特别为你第一
Peter 3 and
彼得3和
verse six is what we're in or verse
诗六等于什么我们或诗句
seven is what we're interested in first
七是我们首先感兴趣的
Peter 3:7 and says you husband's
彼得后书3：7并说你丈夫的
likewise likewise live with your wives
同样也和你的妻子住在一起
in an understanding way as a weaker
作为一个较弱的理解方式
vessel now in this particular context
船只现在在这个特定的背景下
first Peter was written to believers who
第一个彼得写给信徒们
were struggling with the hardships that
与艰辛都在努力说
unbelievers are bringing into their life
不信的人正在带来他们的生活
so we can probably safely say within
所以我们可以安全地说出来
context this is written to a husband who
这是写给丈夫的背景
is married to an unbelieving wife and
嫁给了一个不信的妻子和
this and she's bringing a lot of
这一点，她带来了很多
hardship into his life now I'm not
现在我不是生活困难
saying that Julie's an unbeliever but
说， 朱莉是一个信徒，但
I'm saying this because this is a this
我这样说，因为这是一本
just magnifies his problem and still
只是放大他的问题而且仍然
Peter says that that husband still has a
彼得说那个丈夫还有一个
biblical responsibility to live with his
与他一起生活的圣经责任
wife in an understanding way and in a
妻子以一种理解的方式和一种方式
caring way and in fact the word that's
关心的方式， 实际上是那个词
used there here is to dwell with her
在这里用来和她住在一起
knowledgeably that's the idea to really
知识渊博，这才是真正的想法
know her and that's what we've been
认识她，这就是我们过去的经历
working on we we believe the Word of God
我们努力工作，我们相信上帝的话语
teaches Joe and you're going to find
教乔，你会发现
this out in your ministry again that in
这个在你的事工中再次出现在
order to really be a godly husband
为了真正成为一个敬虔的丈夫
you've got to do more than just bring
你必须做的不仅仅是带来
home a paycheck and do well on your job
在家里领薪水，做好自己的工作
you're going to find yourself saying
你会发现自己在说什么
that over and over again to the men that
那个 男人一遍又一遍地说
you minister to it means making your
你服事它意味着你的
wife a priority that means I think in
妻子的优先权意味着我想到了
dwelling with her knowledgeably that
和知识渊博的人住在一起
means her problems really become your
意味着她的问题真的成了你的
problems when she's struggling with
当她挣扎着问题
depression that means that's just as
抑郁意味着就是这样
much your problem as it is hers and and
很多你的问题，因为它是她的和
living with her as a weaker vessel it
和她一样生活在一个较弱的船上
doesn't necessarily mean that women are
并不一定意味着女性
physically weaker I don't think that's
身体虚弱我不认为那是
what it's saying at all I mean there's
我所说的完全是什么意思
some women you go into these health
有些女性你会进入这些健康状态
clubs and they're out there lifting
俱乐部，他们在那里解除
weights and everything it doesn't
重量和它没有的一切
necessarily mean that but what it does
必然意味着它的作用
mean is that I like to translate this
意思是我喜欢翻译这个
and treat her as a delicate vase that'd
并把她当成那会一个微妙的花瓶
be a good way to do it a piece of
是一个很好的办法做到这一点 的一块
pottery that's delicate like a fine
陶器那种精致的细腻
piece of
一块
China all right a lot of guys treat
中国没事了很多人的治疗
their wives like Tupperware instead of
他们的妻子喜欢特百惠而不是
China yeah all right but no that's not
中国没关系，但不是没有
the goal here the goal is to be gentle
这里的目标是温柔
caring and loving in relationship to
关心和爱的关怀
your wife so that means her problems in
你的妻子这意味着她的问题
terms of depression become your problems
抑郁症的症状成为你的问题
and it the the encouragement that that
并鼓励那样做
will give to her is immeasurable to know
会给她不可估量的知识
that she has someone else walking
她有其他人走路
through that problem sometimes your
通过这个问题，有时你的
strength will be sufficient to carry her
力量足以带她
through those dark days and and so you
通过那些黑暗的日子等你
need to be remain strong and firmly
需要保持坚强和坚定
committed to the truth of the word of
致力于真理的话语
God as well so all right I wanted to
上帝也很好，我想
start there because the way in which we
从那里开始，因为我们的方式
ended in our last session now let's take
我们上一次会议结束了现在让我们采取
up and let's take a look at your
我们来看看你的
homework real quickly and see what
功课真快，看看有什么
happens I had given you homework here in
偏偏我曾在这里给你 的功课
regard to Joe we're continuing the work
关于乔，我们继续工作
through the exemplary husband and if you
通过模范丈夫，如果你
want to grab that for a moment and I
我想抓住那一刻
realize that I've asked you to continue
意识到我已经要求你继续
to highlight several significant
突出几个重要的
statements that will help you that
有助于你的陈述
really help you in this situation
在这种情况下真的能帮到你
understand what your role should be what
了解你的角色应该是什么
you should do in relationship to Julie I
你应该在关系朱莉我做
just want you to kind of flip through
只是想让你有点翻身
there for a moment and because of our
那一刻，因为我们的
time today we want to zero in on
今天一次我们要零上
probably a couple of the more
可能还有几个
significant things that really sort of
真正有意义的重要事情
hit you between the eyes what what did
什么做了什么打你的眼睛
you find out there I think just first of
你发现那里我认为只是第一个
all the definition that is clearly
所有的定义都很清楚
presented of what biblical love is and
介绍了圣经中的爱是什么
how it can be warped when you're
它是如何被扭曲的
throwing it through the grid of my wants
把它扔进我想要的网格
and my needs and ministry
以及我的需要和事工
responsibilities and even things at home
在家里的责任，甚至是事情
that are going on or sexual
正在发生或性行为
dissatisfaction or other things of that
不满或其它东西
nature where it becomes more of a self
它变得更像是一种自我
seeking self gratifying love where my
在我的地方寻求自我满足的爱
needs aren't being met yeah good she's
需求没有得到满足是的，她是好的
not fulfilling the responsibilities that
没有履行责任
I want her to fulfill in ministry in
我希望她在事工中完成
other kind of ways and so I think it was
其他方式， 所以我认为是
just helpful to get back to
只是有助于回到
to a biblical definition that true love
一个圣经的定义，真正的爱
is not defined by our circumstances
不是由我们的情况定义的
around us or by our own feelings of what
在我们周围或者我们自己有什么感受
we need
我们需要
Liz defined by Jesus Christ and him
利兹由耶稣基督和他定义
laying down his life for me and my
为我和我的生命奠定了生命
satisfaction of my love life is found
我的爱情生活的满意度被发现
only in him it's not satisfied by her
只有在他身上才不满足于她
it's not satisfied by a successful
成功并不满足
ministry
部
I am completely sufficient and satisfied
我完全足够和满意
with the love of Christ alone and
只有基督的爱和
anything over the top that she's able to
任何东西在上面，她的能
contribute is it is more than that it
贡献是它不仅仅是它
doesn't diminish it and it doesn't
不会减少它，也不会减少它
necessarily increase it but so that was
必然会增加它，但事实就是如此
that was just very helpful for me good
这仅仅是非常有帮助，我很好
you know sometimes we say - we say two
你知道有时我们说 - 我们说两个
teenagers who struggle with sexual sin
与性罪斗争的青少年
we say to them listen no one ever died
我们对他们说听，没有人死过
without it all right now we'll die
没有它 ，现在好了 ，我们会死
without food we'll die without water but
没有食物我们会在没有水的情况下死去但是
no one ever died now obviously in terms
从来没有人明显死过
of her wifely responsibilities in terms
她而言妻子的责任
of your husband Lee responsibilities we
你的丈夫李某我们的责任
have a responsibility as 1st Corinthians
作为哥林多前书有责任
7 3 says to fulfill our spouses to make
7 3说要完成我们的配偶
sure that their needs are met in those
确保他们的需求得到满足
areas but at the same time we also have
区域，但同时我们也有
a responsibility to be understanding
有责任去理解
when our husbands or our wives are
当我们的丈夫或我们的妻子
struggling with issues that distract
与分散的问题挣扎
them away from that so that's what we're
他们远离那个，所以我们就是这样
looking for to you I mean your wife has
寻找你我的意思是你的妻子
been going through a period of pretty
经历了一段漂亮的时期
serious suffering difficulty so you're
严重的痛苦困难，所以你
gonna have to be understanding your and
必须要了解你的和
have to be tender during these times and
必须要在这些时间和招标
and God is going to see you both through
上帝会看到你们两个
this maze all right and already we've
这个迷宫很好，我们已经
seen some changes and we're really
看到一些变化，我们真的
grateful for that we want to build on
感谢 我们要建立在
that success so that's good all right
成功，这样就可以了
good what else did you find out in that
你还发现了 什么呢？
chapter um I I found just really helpful
第二章我发现真的很有帮助
the list that Stuart Scott gives on just
Stuart Scott给出的清单
proud thoughts to put off and loving
骄傲的想法推迟和爱
thoughts to put on and pride definitely
坚持不懈的想法和自豪感
as we found in in our previous sessions
正如我们之前的会议中所发现的那样
it's such a root of my own selfishness
这是我自私的根源
lack of understanding and living with
缺乏理解和生活
her in an understanding way every day of
她每天都以理解的方式
our marriage and so I think just a
我们的婚姻，所以我认为只是一个
couple of those proud thoughts to put
几次这样的想法感到骄傲放
off that we're helpful to look at we're
关闭我们看看我们是有帮助的
number one the selfish thought to put
第一个自私的想法
off that he lists here is I will do this
他在这里列出的是我会这样做的
as she will do this and how easy that is
因为她会这样做，这是多么容易
to get into my own thinking that yeah
进入我自己的思想，是啊
I'm going to to serve her in this way to
我打算以这种方式为她服务
give her a good example because I expect
给她一个很好的例子，因为我期待
her to do that in return yes and knowing
她这样做是为了回报是和知道
full well that you know she may not do
你知道她可能不会这样做
that and so that may cause me to not
那可能导致我没有
respond that way again but it's just a
再次回应， 但它只是一个
selfish motivation it's not from a pure
自私的动机不是纯粹的
heart it's from one that's seeking self
这是一个寻求自我的人
gratification and for her to meet my
满足和她见到我的
needs and not doing it out of it an
需要而不是从中做出来的
unselfish caring mode they're so good
无私的关怀模式，他们是如此的好
that's good I think that whole process
这很好我认为整个过程
though is something that I hope to learn
虽然是我希望学习的东西
more about as far as just the practical
更多关于实用性
discipline of putting off those sinful
推迟那些罪恶的纪律
problem selfish thoughts and putting on
问题自私的想法和穿上
god-honoring thoughts ones that please
敬意的敬神思想
her and doing what she would like to do
她做了她想做的事
right alright hey let me ask you a
好吧，嘿，让我问你一个
question about that have you gotten to
问题有关你读懂了
the point where you actually sought her
你真正寻找她的地方
forgiveness on these things I have and
宽恕我拥有的这些东西
that's something that again I think
那是我想的那件事
could use some more work as far as that
可以使用更多的工作
that whole process yeah in thinking
整个过程是的，在思考
through what what is biblical
通过什么是圣经
forgiveness the full extent because it
宽恕，因为它
seems like the same things at times keep
似乎有些事情有时保持
coming up and you keep confessing them
来了，你继续承认他们
and what's what's the the biblical
什么是圣经
process for changing behavior so that
改变行为的过程
I'm actually growing through that I
我实际上正在成长
think the initial thing is fine to
认为最初的事情是要罚款
repent and to desire to turn to pray
悔改并渴望转向祈祷
about it but to somehow think that by
这件事，但是莫名其妙地认为，通过
osmosis I'm just going to change just
渗透我只是要改变
after I repent there's there's work and
在我忏悔之后，那里有工作和
it's discipline and I am I am learning
这是纪律，我在学习
to grow in that area yeah good well
在那个地区成长是的好
biblical repentance is a change of mind
圣经的悔改是改变主意的
that is so complete that it leads to a
这是如此完整，它导致了一个
complete change of life alright that's
完全改变生活就好了
biblical repentance and if you genuinely
圣经忏悔， 如果你真的
have confessed that to Julie then part
已经承认朱莉然后分手了
of that confession and repenting of it
它是认罪和悔改的
means I really got to change as a
意味着我真的需要改变
husband I realize that I've got to
老公， 我意识到我必须这样做
change
更改
so do you recall him coming to you Julie
所以你还记得他来找你Julie
and saying I need to ask you forgiveness
并说我需要请你原谅
for not being the caring kind of husband
因为她不是一个充满爱心的丈夫
in this way that I need to be okay
通过这种方式， 我需要是好的
that's good and were you able to forgive
这很好，你能原谅
him yeah I think that's a process dude
他是啊我认为这是一个过程家伙
yeah okay
好的
yeah all right yeah yeah when we give
是的， 是的，是的，当我们给予的时候
our word that means and we alluded to
这意味着我们所提到的
this back in our second session but that
这回到了我们的第二次会议，但那
means number one when we seek
当我们寻求时，意味着第一
forgiveness of one another and we're in
彼此的宽恕和我们在一起
that forgiveness is granted number one
宽恕被授予第一名
I'm not going to bring this up and throw
我不打算把它拿出去扔
this up in your face again and and
这再一次在你的脸上和
thereby hurt you and number two I'm not
从而伤害了你，我不是
going to go around talk about it behind
要四处谈论它
your back number three I'm not going to
你的后三号我不打算
dwell on in my own heart in mind and
记住我自己的心灵
become bitter so I'm not going to bring
变得很苦， 所以我不会带来
it up to you I'm not going to bring it
由你决定我不打算带它
up to others and I'm not going to bring
取决于其他人，我不会带来
it up to myself all right just just
它以自己没事才刚刚
doing a quick review on that that's what
快速回顾那是什么
needs to happen well praise God for his
需要好好赞美上帝为他的
work through his word in Joe and Julie
通过他在乔和朱莉的话语
we saw the beginnings of change right
我们看到了变革的开始
there
那里
and God has done the beginning of what
而上帝已经做了什么的开始
only he can do in hearts
只有他才能在心中做到
you
您